sportslocate.com 2016-11-17

# Privacy Policy | SportsLocate

**Privacy Policy**

Customer information is collected for the purpose of making your life easier.  We use the information to process orders, improve our platform and inform our customer service team.  By collecting this information our platform operates better, faster and more conveniently for our customers.

The disclosure of personal information will never occur without your express consent.

As SportsLocate evolves, changes will likely be made to this privacy policy.  We will not reduce your rights without your express consent.  Policy updates will be dated and posted to this page and significant changes will be emailed to our user base.

SportsLocate.com allows facilities to create and promote offers for athletes using SportsLocate.com.  To use SportsLocate.com, facilities and athletes alike must create individual SportsLocate.com accounts.

We may allow you to create an account using your Facebook® or other third party service account (your Social Login).  We will not keep, share or use your Social Login except to provide our Services.

If you are a facility, we may require you to verify and/or provide personal and business information when you claim a SportsLocate.com facility profile or create your SportsLocate.com account.  This information may include your name, email address, business name and location.  Any personal information about you will be used by us only in connection with your facility profile and to provide our Services.

If you use SportsLocate.com to purchase services or membership offered by a facility, you may be prompted to enter an email address and/or other personal information.   We may provide all such information you enter in connection with redeeming an offer at SportsLocate.com to the facility that posted the offer.  We are not responsible for any subsequent use of such information by the facility or any third party.

We do not store any credit card numbers in our system except to process and transmit the information for payment processing. If you enter your credit card information to redeem an offer or purchase services at SportsLocate.com, that information is encrypted and transmitted immediately for processing and authorization. Once the transaction is authorized, we delete the credit card information from our system. If the services you purchase require recurring billing, your information is encrypted and maintained by our payment processing provider.

We may use, publish or transfer data and statistics about the use of our Services by athletes, facilities or other users in aggregate or anonymous form in our discretion.  Also, our customer and user lists are assets of SportsLocate.com LLC and may be transferred together with our website and business in our discretion.
